Anthony Micco

491 Oakridge Drive • Youngstown, Ohio, 44512 • (330) 881-8284 • anthonymicco2003@gmail.com

Objective

I am a second year Computer Science and Mathematics double major at Youngstown State University. I am currently pursuing an internship in the field to continue to learn and grow as a programmer as well as gain valuable experience and skills to be a successful software developer.

Education

Youngstown State University, Youngstown, OH

Aug 2021-Present

Working to obtain Bachelor's Degrees in Computer Science and Mathematics.

Boardman High School, Boardman, OH

Aug 2017-June 2021

• Obtained my high school diploma and graduated with a 4.0 GPA.

Skills

- Programming experience in C++, Java, CSS, Javascript and SQL
- Ability to effectively collaborate with coworkers
- Clearly and effectively communicate with peers
- Diligently and meticulously accomplish assigned tasks
- Eagerness to ask questions and learn
- Ability to critically think and work through and solve problems

Work Experience

Computer Technology Intern

Jan 2023-Present

Boardman Local Schools, Boardman, OH

- Carefully and efficiently replace broken Chromebook screens
- Provide technical support to teachers throughout school district
- Manage and update inventory of district's devices

Assistant Freshman and Junior Varsity Football Coach

July 2022-Present

Boardman Local Schools, Boardman, OH

- Effectively demonstrate techniques and drills
- Assisted in rotating athletes in and out during competitions
- Carefully brokedown fil to prepare gameplan

Landscaper June 2019-Sept 2022

Clear Cut Stump Grinding, Canfield, OH

- Diligently removed wood chips from work site
- Efficiently wheeled topsoil and landscape rock to work site
- Carefully spread grass seed and fertilizer

Projects

Fitness Workout Tracker

January 2023-Present

- Collaborating with a fellow computer science major to develop a fitness web-app using Javascript and CSS
- Features include ability to upload workouts including number of sets, reps and weight
- Currently working to implement calorie tracking so users can track daily meals and snacks